http://www.jubileefireworks.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy - Jubilee Fireworks Retail Store
Skip to content
facebooktwitterinstagram
Contact UsMy Account Remember MeRegisterCart
Home – Buy Fireworks Multishot CakesDiscounted Display PacksRocketsSelection BoxesXL BarragesSingle IgnitionsBarrage PacksFinale ItemsMines & CandlesLow NoiseNeighbourhood FriendlyGender RevealWheels & FountainsSparklers / MiscellaneousFlares & SmokesAboutSafetyFireworks ShopDisplaysContact
Products search
Search
Home – Buy Fireworks Multishot CakesDiscounted Display PacksRocketsSelection BoxesXL BarragesSingle IgnitionsBarrage PacksFinale ItemsMines & CandlesLow NoiseNeighbourhood FriendlyGender RevealWheels & FountainsSparklers / MiscellaneousFlares & SmokesAboutSafetyFireworks ShopDisplaysContact
Products search
Search
Home – Buy Fireworks Multishot CakesDiscounted Display PacksRocketsSelection BoxesXL BarragesSingle IgnitionsBarrage PacksFinale ItemsMines & CandlesLow NoiseNeighbourhood FriendlyGender RevealWheels & FountainsSparklers / MiscellaneousFlares & SmokesAboutSafetyFireworks ShopDisplaysContact
Home/Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyPJ Whitby2020-09-10T15:56:25+00:00
PRIVACY
Privacy Policy – Jubilee Fireworks
This page will be regularly updated to show you all the things we do with your personal data. This policy applies if you’re a client (purchaser), supplier, or partner.
About Jubilee Fireworks
http://www.jubileefireworks.co.uk is a site operated by Jubilee Fireworks Ltd. We are registered at Unit 29 Dawley Trading Estate, Stallings Lane, Kingswinford, West Midlands, DY6 7AP.
This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website, or others associated with our company.
Things covered in the privacy policy:
What information we collect about you?
How will we use this information about you?
Marketing
Access to your information and correction
Cookies
Other websites
Changes to our privacy policy
How to contact us
What information do we collect about you?
Your personal data is any information which identifies you, or which can be identified as relating to you personally for example, name, address, phone number, email address that may be collected and used by us. We’ll only collect the personal data that we need.
We collect information about you when you register your interest in our board games, contact us via phone, email or place an order for products or services. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and use offers. Website usage information is collected using cookies so we are able to provide users with a better experience.
The personal data you give us may include name, title, address, employment status, demographic information, email address, telephone numbers, personal description, photographs, CCTV images, attitudes, opinions, usernames and passwords.
How will we use the information about you?
We collect information about you to manage your account and, with your consent, to email you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you. We will only process your personal data for legitimate purposes as set by the General Data Protection Regulations (from 30th January 2019).
Jubilee Fireworks Ltd will not share your information for marketing purposes with other companies, we will only share your details with organisations when necessary in order to fulfil our service to you and where the privacy and security of your data is assured. In processing your order, we may send your details to, and also use information from credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.
Marketing
If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. You have the right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes.
Access to your information and correction
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email *protected email* or write to us at the following address, Unit 29 Dawley Trading Estate, Stallings Lane, Kingswinford, West Midlands, DY6 7AP for the attention of Data Officer. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.
Cookies
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.
For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.
You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.
Other websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to our website. If you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies. We are not liable for the information provided through these links.
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This Privacy policy was last updated on 20th August 2020. We are required by law to provide any information we hold to fraud agencies, the police or government agencies when summoned to do so.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or the information we hold about you:
By email: *protected email*
Write to us: Unit 29 Dawley Trading Estate, Stallings Lane, Kingswinford, West Midlands, DY6 7AP
29 Dawley Trading Estate,
Stallings Lane,
Kingswinford,
DY6 7AP
Phone: 01384 402255
Email: *protected email*
Web:
www.jubileefireworks.com
Products search
Search
Jubilee Fireworks Ltd.     All rights reserved.
Site Built By PJW
